Southwest Folklore Center Cassette Recordings Collection, 1975-1995
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Navajo love songs, vol. 5, The Klagetoh Swingers, 1982; Taos, N.M., Indian House, p1982; 1 sound cassette, analog, stereo; NOTES: Photograph of The Klagetoh Swingers on cover... Insert contains a black and white photograph of The Klagetoh Swingers; information about the group and their music... Recorded at Klagetoh, Arizona, on July 30, 1980... Singers include: Ted B. Bonnie; Ned Tsosie Clark; Frank J. Begay; Robert P. Roan; Arthur P. Roan; Bennie Silversmith; Johnny Dealison... Spin dance songs: Calling my sweetheart -- Squaw dance is near -- Skip dance songs: Is it okay? -- Flirting with a Spanish girl -- I wish I could go back with her -- She's the one -- Apache girl and her grandmother -- Zuni girl from Gallup -- Lonesome Valley -- Two girls call me darling -- You make me lonesome, woman -- First night I danced with her -- I started thinking about you -- Uncle Sam's pension -- Let's go under the shade -- Our home is far, let's go -- Foot racing at Window Rock Fair -- Santo Domingo girl stood me up --; SWF 87.14/C.24
- Navajo social songs, 1972; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1972; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Seventeen squaw dance songs (by Robert E. Lee) -- Nineteen squaw dance songs (by Robert E. Lee) --; SWF 87.14/C.25
- Navajo, 1972; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1972; 1 sound cassette, analog; Round dance -- Train to Gallup -- Sonnie, I'm leaving -- Grinding songs -- Old Glory on Iwo Jima -- Let's hope for love -- Rhythm squaw dance -- Do not forsake me -- Hoop dance -- Goat song -- Sun dance song -- My arms around your neck -- Riding songs -- Yei be chai chant -- Old Glory on Iwo Jima --; SWF 87.14/C.26
- Nanaba Midge sings traditional Navajo songs, Midge, Nanaba, 1985; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of Nanaba Midge on cover... Song descriptions included inside cover... Mother Earth -- Thanks to my Father in Heaven -- Together we will walk in beauty -- Navajo flag song -- Handsome cowboy -- Can you come home with me? -- You are handsome and I want you -- A Blessing for the soldier -- A Blessing for the baby -- I walk in beauty -- I'm proud to be a Diné woman -- I think of you every day --; SWF 87.14/C.27
- Navajo corn grinding and shoe game songs, Corn Grinding Singers and Shoe Game Singers, 1975; Taos, N.M., Indian House, p1975; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph on cover of Navajo corn grinding... Members of the Corn Grinding Singers and the Shoe Game Singers listed on cover... Mary Johnson, corn grinder... Recorded at Klagetoh, Arizona, on April 21, 1974 and November 10, 1974... 7 corn grinding songs -- 4 shoe game songs -- 9 shoe game songs --; SWF 87.14/C.28
- Navajo love songs, vol. 6, The Klagetoh Swingers, 1982; Taos, N.M., Indian House, p1975; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph on cover of The Klagetoh Swingers... Insert contains a black and white photograph of The Klagetoh Swingers; information about the group and their music... Recorded at Klagetoh, Arizona, July 30, 1980... Singers include; Ted B. Bonnie; Ned Tsosie Clark; Frank J. Begay; Robert P. Roan; Arthur P. Roan; Bennie Silversmith; Johnny Dealison... One by one -- Salt Lake City woman -- Oklahoma bicycle -- You have a new vehicle -- She happens to be my cousin -- Who's sweetheart was she last summer? -- My Spanish girlfriend feeds me Masa Harina -- The Granddaughter led me wrong -- Barrel racer from Window Rock -- Mexican girl, introduce yourself -- Blue-eyed girl with curley hair --; SWF 87.14/C.29
- Night and daylight Yebichei, 1972; Taos, N.M., Indian House, p1972; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Recorded at Klagetoh, Arizona, March 2, 1968... Singers include: Boniface Bonnie; Autisdy Smith; M.D. Johnson; Roy Bonnie; Ben J. Johnson; Benny Roan Hourse; Ted Bonnie; Donald Deal... 5 daylight songs -- 5 night songs --; SWF 87.14/C.30
- Navajo peyote ceremonial songs, vol.1, Wilson, Aronith, Jr. and Hanson Ashley, 1981; Taos, N.M., Indian House, p1981; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Cover contains a photograph of the singers, Wilson Aronith, Jr. (grandson of Dlin-Di-Bah) and Hanson Ashely (grandson of Yah-De-Bah)... Recorded at Wheatfield, Arizona, on October 20, 1979... Recording contains sacred peyote ceremonial songs... Insert includes a black and white photograph of Wilson Aronith and Hanson Ashley; information about the Dine's peyote story by Wilson Aronith; interpretations and translations of the songs by Wilson Aronith and Hanson Ashley...; SWF 87.14/C.31
- Navajo peyote ceremonial songs, vol.2, Wilson, Aronith Jr. and Hanson Ashley, 1981; Taos, N.M., Indian House, p1981; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Cover includes photograph of the singers, Wilson Aronith, Jr. (grandson of Dlin-Di-Bah) and Hanson Ashley (grandson of Yah-De-Bah)... Recorded at Wheatfield, Arizona, on October 20, 1979... Recording contains sacred peyote ceremonial songs... Insert includes a black and white photograph of Wilson Aronith and Hanson Ashley; information about the Dine's peyote story by Wilson Aronith; interpretations and translations of the songs by Wilson Aronith and Hanson Ashley...; SWF 87.14/C.32
- Navajo Wildcat Peak, vol.1: Morning peyote songs, Navajo Wildcat Peak, 1977; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1977; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Recording contains twentyseven songs... 15 morning peyote songs -- 12 morning peyote songs --; SWF 87.14/C.35
- Navajo Wildcat Peak, vol.2: Peyote songs, Navajo Wildcat Peak, 1978; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1978; 1 sound cassette, analog; SWF 87.14/C.36
- Navajo Wildcat Peak, volume 3: Morning peyote songs (twenty-five songs), Navajo Wildcat Peak, 1979; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1979; 1 sound cassette, analog; Twelve songs -- Thirteen songs; SWF 87.14/C.37
- Morning peyote songs, volume 4, Navajo Wildcat Peak, 1980; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1980; 1 sound cassette, analog; Morning peyote songs --; SWF 87.14/C.38
- Morning peyote songs, volume 5, Navajo Wildcat Peak, 1987; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1987; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Cover art by Archie P. Williams... Recorded February 23, 1987, by Raymond Boley... 13 Peyote songs -- 13 Peyote songs --; SWF 87.14/C.39
- 36 Morning peyote songs, Wildcat Peak Youth (Navajo), 1981; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1981; 1 sound cassette, analog; Morning peyote songs --; SWF 87.14/C.40
- In loving memories, Curtis, Johnny, 1981; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1981; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol.4; NOTES: Cover design by Richard Embry... Title on cover, "In Loving Memories, Johnny Curtis, Apache Gospel Singer"... Dedication: "To Toodie and all those who have gone before"... Musicians include: Johnny Curtis, vocals lead and rhythm guitar; Melvin Antonio, bass; Roddy Pilcher, drums; Peter Antonio, rhythm guitar; Leon Antonio, drums; Johnathan Graham, keyboards; James "Red" Godwin, drums; Don Kowitt, steel guitar; Tom West, harmonica; Robert Doyle, producer; Ray Boley, executive producer... I need you (Johnny Curtis) -- Mansion in the sky -- Precious memories -- I don't know about tomorrow -- Roses never fade -- King Jesus -- How beautiful heaven must be -- Amazing grace -- I must tell Jesus -- I just came to talk -- City of gold -- Thinking about my lost friends (Johnny Curtis) --; SWF 87.14/C.41
- Apache country gospel, Curtis, Johnny, 1977; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1977; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol. 1; NOTES: Musicians: Johnny Curtis, lead guitar and vocals; David C. Seville, bass; Freddie Ringlaro, drums; David Forester, rhythm... Romans six 23 (J. Curtis) -- Balaam (Num.22:22) (J. Curtis) -- Help me to understand you (J. Curtis) -- Old things are passed away (J. Curtis) -- Thank you Jesus (J. Curtis) -- Bron to love the Lord (Arr. by J. Curtis) -- Jesus answers prayer (J. Curtis) -- Neither by the blood (M. Johanning) -- Take my yoke upon you (J. Curtis) --; SWF 87.14/C.42
- Spirit of God, Curtis, Johnny, 1984; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Cover art: "Appeal to the Great Spirit," courtesy of Coffrin's Old West Gallery, Miles City, Montana... Dedication: "I want to give special thanks to the Lord Jesus Christ for making this album possible. Special Thanks also goes to my mother, Sister Lousie Burits, Rev. Gene Martin of Atlanta, Georgia, Edwina Beaumont of Billings, Montana, Madeline (Maggie) Harrina of Whiteriver, Arizona for the use of their songs, and to the Christian Utes of Towaoc, Colorade. This album is in memory of the late Sister Nancy Jefferson of Lodge Grass, Montana"... Johnny Curtis, executive producer... Recorded, mixed and remixed by Jay Cummins at Right Track Studio, Poplar, Montana... Information on tribal affiliations of band members on cover... Musicians: Johnnny Curtis, lead and backup vocals, percussion, rhythm, lead and acoustic guitar; Jay Cummis, backup vocals, bass, drums, percussion, rhythm, lead acoustic and steel guitar, piano, organ and synthesizer; Melvin Antonio, bass on "Lullaby of the Prodigal Son"; Bob Boni, drums on "Lullaby of the Prodigal Son"... Spirit of God (N. Jefferson) -- Awake, awake (L. Curtis) -- Praise the Lord, o ye people (L. Curtis) -- Oh, bless that wonderful name (N. Jefferson) -- Moon of the strong cold winds (J. Curtis) -- I'm just praising the Lord (Rev. Gene Martin) -- Lullaby of the prodigal son (J. Curtis) -- Lead us by thy way (L. Curtis) -- No one cares for me (E. Beaumont) -- Prayer to the great spirit (L. Curtis) -- Lord, you've been good to me (M. Harrina) --; SWF 87.14/C.44
- Johnny Curtis and the Apache Gospel Sounds, Curtis, Johnny and the Apache Gospel Sounds, 1980; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1980; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of Johnny Curtis and the Apache Gospel Sounds on cover... Musicians: Johnny Curtis, guitar and vocals, Melvin Antonio, bass; C. Roddy Pilcher, drums; Leon Antonio, drums; Jonathan Graham, organ... Members of the Apache Gospel Sounds singers listed on cover... Beloved -- Farewell -- Mansion over the hilltop -- Jesus knows -- Power -- Glory, glory -- Oh, children -- Take me back -- Hold my hand (in Apache) -- When the saints go marching in --; SWF 87.14/C.45
- Leavin' this reservation, Apache gospel rock, Curtis, Johnny, 1978; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1978; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of Johnny Curtis on cover... Musicians: Johnny Curtis, lead guitar and lead vocals; Mike Johanning, harmony; James "Red" Godwin and Leon Antonio, drums; Jonathan Graham, keyboards; Melvin Antonio, bass; Michael Hardwick, steel guitar, Devore Thompson, producer; Dennis Alexander, engineer... Leavin this reservation -- Come and go with me -- Be nice -- East Fork song -- Give me love -- Go now Moses -- Use me one more time -- Forever God -- Sweet comfort -- New found friend -- Soon coming King -- Lord how I love you -- Heaven bound --; SWF 87.14/C.46
- Live in concert, Curtis, Johnny, 1987; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records Productions, Inc., p1987; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol.7; NOTES: Photograph of Johnny Curtis on cover... Title on cover, "Live in Concert", Johnny Curtis, Indian Gospel Singer"... Recorded in concert, April 12, 1986, at Window Rock Civic Center, Arizona... Dedication: "This album is dedicated to my parents, brother Paul and sister Louise Curtis. My thanks to all my supporters, fans and peoples of all Indian Nations"... Musicians: Johnny Curtis, lead vocals, lead and rhythm guitar; Jay Cummins, keyboards, back up vocals; Peter Antonio, rhythm guitar; James Antonio, drums; Melvin Antonio, bass; Raymond A. Boley and Johnny Curtis, executive producers... Recorded and mixed by Jack Cummins, Right Track Studio, Poplar, Montana... Guardian angel (Johnny Curtis) -- Can't you see, first love (Johnny Curtis) -- Let me feel the love of my Jesus -- I really want to thank you (Andrae Crouch) -- Real -- Revival preacher (Johnny Curtis) -- They just go by -- You're beautiful (arranged by Johnny Curtis) -- He'll roll your burdens away (Alex Lewis) -- He is mine (Nancy Jefferson) -- Talk to me (Timmy Hinton) --; SWF 87.14/C.47
- Chinle Galileans, volume one, Chinle Galileans, 1975; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, Produced by Diné Records, p1975; 1 sound cassette, analog; Lord I will go -- Lovest Thou me -- Seek ye the Lord -- God is God -- Jesus said it -- Evangelize the world -- I shall not be moved -- I saw the face of Jesus -- Grant a miracle -- Where could I go -- Just a few more days -- He touched me -- I shall not be moved -- I saw the face of Jesus -- Grant a miracle -- Where could I go -- Just a few more days -- He touched me --; SWF 87.14/C.48
- Chinle Galileans, volume three, Chinle Galileans, 1979; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, Produced by Diné Records, p1979; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Date of publication on cover, 1978... King Jesus -- Let my light shine -- It won't be long -- The Secret -- Redemption draweth nigh -- No more time -- Let me be there -- Try a little kindness -- Say "I do" -- How great Thou art --; SWF 87.14/C.49
- Introducing the Gospel Light Singers, Gospel Light Singers, 1978; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1978; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of the Gospel Light Singers on cover... Musicians: Alfred Larry Jim; Cynthia Jim; Sharon Yazzie; Louise Jim; William Tso; Stanley Jim... Where could I go -- He knows -- Precious Jesus, don't forget -- Sweet by and by -- Amazing grace -- Jericho Road -- Jesus is the love of man -- East gate -- At the cross -- When morning comes -- How great Thou art -- Tell me the story --; SWF 87.14/C.50
- Jesus died for me long ago, Gospel Light Singers, 1979; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1979; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of Gospel Light Singers on cover... Dedication: "Songs of hope dedicated to Ned H. Tso, Etta R. Harvey, Rev. Allen Y. Hill, and all brothers and sisters who proceeded us into Gloryland"... Tom Tso, manager... Jesus died for me long ago -- Angels rock me to sleep -- Lord lead me on -- Precious memories -- The Lord is my shepherd -- No tears in heaven -- Where the soul never dies -- Getting ready to leave this world -- I'll fly away -- Where roses never fade -- Hold to God's unchanging hand -- Further along --; SWF 87.14/C.51
- To my mansion in the sky, Gospel Light Singers, 1980; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1980; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol.3; NOTES: Painting on cover by Kinzie D. Yazza... Musicians: Alfred Larry Jim; Cynthia Jim; Sharon Yazzie; Louise Jim; William Tso; Stanley Jim... To my mansion in the sky -- I will never turn back -- Keep on believing -- Holy be thy name -- I want to walk as close as I possibly can -- Leaning on the everlasting arm -- New Jerusalem -- I'm standing on the solid rock -- How can I ever praise my Lord enough -- God will provide -- After Calvary, close to thee --; SWF 87.14/C.52
- Life's railway to heaven, Gospel Light Singers, 1982; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1982; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol.4; NOTES: Photograph of the Gospel Light Singers on cover... Musicians: Sharon Yazzie; Cynthia Jim; Lousie Jim; Kerlena Ann Tso; Alfred Larry Jim; Stanley Him; William Tso; Paul Bitsuie... It's been done -- Oh come angel band -- A Beautiful life -- Blesseth light shine on (in Navajo) -- Let my life shine -- Beulahland -- Redemption draweth, Jesus hold my hand (in Navajo) -- Come unto me -- Life's railway to heaven -- Just a little talk with Jesus -- Matthew 24 --; SWF 87.14/C.53
- I'm bound for that city, Gospel Light Singers, 1983; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1983; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol.5; NOTES: Cover art by Eugene Joe... Musicians: William Tso, lead guitar and vocals; Girdy Tso, bass; Johnathan Tso, acoustic rhythm guitar; Paul Bitsuie, steel guitar and vocals; Johnnie Nargo, drums... Old country church -- Born to serve the Lord -- Build my mansion next door to Jesus -- This world is not my home -- Consider the lilies, Lord -- You make a way -- The Uncloudy day -- He's my reason for living -- I'm bound for that city -- Greater is He -- House of gold -- Soon coming King (written by Johnnie Curtis) --; SWF 87.14/C.54
- If that isn't love, Gospel Light Singers, 1986; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Musicians: William Tso, lead and back-up vocals, guitar; Diane Henderson, lead vocals; Girdy Tso, bass guitar; Johnson Dinae, fiddle; Jonathan Tso, acoustic guitar; Johnny Nargo, drums; Timothy Hayes, steel guitar, harmonica, dobro; Emmett Fowler, piano, synthesizer DX-7, back-up vocals; Frankie Woodis, electric guitar... If that isn't love -- Good Samaritan -- Lord feed your children -- I don't deserve a mansion -- One more valley -- Because He lives -- He walks with me -- When the world is on fire -- I don't have to worry anymore -- Green pastures -- Desert song -- Jesus loves you --; SWF 87.14/C.55
- Nizhonie Christmas, Arbor Shade Gospel Singers, 1981; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, Sponsored by Shonto Church of the Nazarene, Shonto, Arizona, p1981; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From cover, "Cover design inspired by a Robert Draper painting"... Singers: Etta Smallcanyon; Marion Begay; Margaret Betgay; Keith Begay; Nita Foster; Tallethea Chischilly... Musicians: Lewis Calamity, Jr.,; Jerry Calamity; Arnold Smallcanyon; Damon Bahe; Rev. Lewis Calamity, Sr., manager...O come all ye faithful (in Navajo and English) -- Go tell it on the mountain (in Navajo) -- Come on, ring the bells -- Away in a manger (in Navajo) -- Joy to the world (in Navajo and English) -- What child is this? -- While shepherds watched their flocks (in Navajo) -- O come, o come Emmanuel -- Hark! The herald angels sing (in Navajo) -- Mary's boychild -- Silent night! Holy Night! (in Navajo) -- We wish you a merry Christmas --; SWF 87.14/C.56
- What a beautiful day!, Arbor Shade Gospel Singers, 1981; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, Produced by Ray Boley and Robert Doyle, Sponsored by the Shonto Church of the Nazarene, Shonto, Arizona, p1981; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Musicians include: Etta Smallcanyon, harmonizer; Margaret Begay, alto; Marion Begay, soprano; Ellouise Calamity, soprano; Tallethea Calamity, soprano; Lewis Calamity, Jr., lead guitar; Jerry Calamity, rhythm guitar; Arnold Smallcanyon, bass; Russell Smallcanyon, acoustic guitar; Roland Smallcanyon, drums; Rosilyn Black, music guitar; Amos Neztsosie, recording advisor; Rev. Lewis Calamity, manager... Amazing grace (in Navajo) -- Standing on the solid rock -- What heaven means to me -- Thank you Lord -- What a beautiful day -- City of gold -- One day too late -- A Song holy angels never sing -- Sheltered in the arms of God -- Ten thousand years --; SWF 87.14/C.57
- Let it shine, Arbor Shade Gospel Singers, 1983; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, Sponsored by Shonto Church of the Nazarene, Shonto, Arizona, p1983; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of singers on cover...Singers: Etta Smallcanyon; Rosilyn Black; Annabelle Smallcanyon; Ellouise Smallcanyon; Marion Begay; Tallethea Chischilly; Nita Foster; Musicians: Lewis Calamity, Jr., lead guitar, vocals; Jerry Calamity, rhythm guitar, vocals; Arnold Smallcanyon, bass; Roland Smallcanyon, drums... Let it shine -- Lord, I want to be a Christian (in Navajo) -- No tears in heaven -- Jesus, Jesus -- I have decided to follow Jesus (in Navajo) -- Come on to Jesus -- Come and go with me (in Navajo) -- My God is real -- At the River Jordan -- Just a closer walk with Thee (in Navajo) -- The Lighthouse -- Life's railway to heaven --; SWF 87.14/C.58
- Peace in the valley, Leupp Sin I'Líinii Singers, 1987; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1987; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Singers: Eunice Begar; LuCinda Paddock; Faith Ann Chatter; Valerie Curley; Louise Monroe; Amy Monroe; Loretta John; Jennie Jensen; Jamie Cody; Annabelle Smallcanyon; Lorena Jack; Rachel Long; Cynthia Wells; Johnny Monroe; Calvin Kelly; Raymond Long, lead guitarist...The Unclouded day (in Navajo) -- Peace in the valley (in Navajo) -- I shall never forget -- It won't be long -- My testimony (in Navajo) -- I'm bound for that city (in Navajo) -- The one who died for me -- Wonderful grace of Jesus (in Navajo) -- Little by little -- Far away is the land; SWF 87.14/C.59
- Songs of the Arizona Apache: Sinew Luke Riley (White Mountain) and Edwin Endfield (San Carlos), Leupp Sin I'Líinii Singers, Riley, Sinew Luke and Edwin Endfield, 1987; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1987; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph on cover by Bob Nuss... Recorded by Ray A. Boley... Song descriptions included on back of cover... Four sunrise ceremonial songs (Changing Woman Ceremony) and two non-ceremonial songs: Apache war dance song (preparation for battle song) -- Social song, "I will travel along with the Creator's blessing" -- "With my prayer I am protected" -- "In this lifetime they know me in the house of clouds" -- "Where are you my girlfriend? We used to walk so nice together" -- "I'm lonesome for San Carlos" -- The white painted lady -- Happy road --; SWF 87.14/C.60
- Remebering Murphy Cassa: Apache-San Carlos, Arizona, Cassa (Casa), Murphy (1910-1980), 1986; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1986; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol.2; NOTES: From cover, "These songs, recorded in the mid-sixties, are the legacy of this noted Apache singer"... Two songs for Gan -- Two deer songs -- Social song -- Two songs for Gan -- Social song -- "Second girl" -- "Oklahoma Trail" --; SWF 87.14/C.61
- Remebering Murphy Cassa: Apache-San Carlos, Arizona, Cassa (Casa), Murphy (1910-1980), 1981; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of performer on cover...From cover, "Noted singer, teller of stories, teacher of the traditional culture of the Apache. These songs, recorded in the mid-sixties, will keep his memory alive"... Sunrise dance -- Song for Gan -- Social dance -- Song for Gan -- Dick Young's prayer chant -- Song for Gan -- Song for Gan -- Song for Gan -- Social song -- Song for Gan -- Song for Gan (healing song) --; SWF 87.14/C.62
- Hopi social dance songs, volume one, 1973; Shungopair, Second Mesa, AZ., Canyon Records, p1973; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Singers include: Bernard Dawahoya; Riley Polequaptewa; Alaric Polequaptewa; Loren Sakeva; Alde Qunyintewa; Seymour Lomakema; Milland Lomakema, Sr.; Milland Lomekema, Jr.; Patrick Lomawaima... From cover, "The songs on this album are social dance songs and are danced from January to mid-May during the time between the killing of the old moon (the full moon) and the beginning of the new moon"... Pauite dance song -- Jemez buffalo dance song -- Zuni buffalo dance song -- Hopi buffalo dance song --; SWF 87.14/C.63
- Hopi butterfly dance, 1970; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1970; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: On cover, "Recorded by Ben Setima on location on the Hopi Mesa of Hoteville, summer of 1967... This is a rare and unique recording - probably the first publicly released recording of an actual Bufferfly Dance in progress on a Hopi mesa"... Information describing the performance of the dance on cover...; SWF 87.14/C.64
- From me to you, Ethelbah, Lee, 1980; Albuqueque, N.M., Alta Vista Recording Studio, Produced by Jose A. Chavez, p1980; 1 sound cassette, analog; Let me be there -- We believe in happy endings -- Heartbreak hotel -- Break my mind -- Armor de Segunda -- Oh lonesome me -- Blue eyes crying in the rain -- Pick me up on your way down -- Don't be angry -- When can we do this again -- Maybe -- Ramblin fever --; SWF 87.14/C.65